members.iinet.net.au 2004-01-13

# iiNet Limited - Privacy Policy

| 

This is the iiNet Privacy Policy, a document which outlines our guarantee on your use of iiNet products. For further information see our Privacy Policy FAQ page.

1\. iiNet uses and may disclose your personal information in order to:  
    (i) Provide services to you;  
    (ii) Research, develop, administer, protect and improve our services;  
    (iii) Instigate debt collection; and  
    (iv) Comply with legal compulsion such as a Court order.  
2\. Other than listed in Clause 1, iiNet will not provide any information which you give to us to any other organisation or individual without your express permission.  
3\. As part of routine administration, iiNet collects system status information such as login times and help desk records. These are not on-sold or disclosed to others except as required in paragraph 1.  
4\. All clients may request access to the personal details collected by iiNet in relation to themselves and the use of the account owned by them. iiNet wishes to ensure that such details are always correct and up-to-date, and will amend any inaccuracies or changes to details on request.  
5\. By law, iiNet must retain some client details for a minimum of 5 years. However, iiNet does not retain clients' personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes of compliance with the law and routine administration.  
6\. If iiNet is ever sold to another organisation, the new owners must also comply with this privacy policy.  
7\. iiNet keeps client information on controlled facilities which are secured against unauthorised access. Proof of identity will be required before information is released to any person, including the client.  
8\. iiNet typically communicates with its clients by email, and sends all clients a newsletter approximately once per month. In exceptional circumstances, urgent notifications may also be sent out by email.  
9\. iiNet is constantly improving and enhancing its services to clients, and may update this privacy policy from time to time. Any changes to the policy will be advised to clients in our regular newsletter and by updating this page on the iiNet web site.  
10\. If you have any queries or comments concerning the privacy policy, call iiNet support on 08 9214 2222 or email [support@iinet.net.au](mailto:support@iinet.net.au).  

Dated the 1st day of September 2000.

|  | 

|   |    
---|---  
  | Privacy Policy FAQ  
  | About iiNet  
  | Product List  
  | Sitemap  
  | iiNet Home Page
